{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820606702","data":{"timestamp":" 946820606702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820609121","data":{"timestamp":" 946820609121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820612594","data":{"timestamp":" 946820612594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820614218","data":{"timestamp":" 946820614218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820618288","data":{"timestamp":" 946820618288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820618463","data":{"timestamp":" 946820618463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820633093","data":{"timestamp":" 946820633092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" d91b7847-216f-4c00-80e6-a8d832b4b5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820647480","data":{"timestamp":" 946820647480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" kuchoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820657375","data":{"timestamp":" 946820657375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820668649","data":{"timestamp":" 946820668649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820698507","data":{"timestamp":" 946820698507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820708612","data":{"timestamp":" 946820708611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820718071","data":{"timestamp":" 946820718071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820736972","data":{"timestamp":" 946820736972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kusikia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820751234","data":{"timestamp":" 946820751234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kusikia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820757024","data":{"timestamp":" 946820757023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820763484","data":{"timestamp":" 946820763484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820771059","data":{"timestamp":" 946820771058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820780908","data":{"timestamp":" 946820780908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820789967","data":{"timestamp":" 946820789967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820795716","data":{"timestamp":" 946820795715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 0712e0d2-17cf-47a1-8679-9728e6f7d9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820806178","data":{"timestamp":" 946820806177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820806407","data":{"timestamp":" 946820806407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820807385","data":{"timestamp":" 946820807384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820808682","data":{"timestamp":" 946820808681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820811643","data":{"timestamp":" 946820811642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820812501","data":{"timestamp":" 946820812501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820812822","data":{"timestamp":" 946820812821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820814065","data":{"timestamp":" 946820814064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820817618","data":{"timestamp":" 946820817616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820818619","data":{"timestamp":" 946820818618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820818885","data":{"timestamp":" 946820818885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820819844","data":{"timestamp":" 946820819844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820822685","data":{"timestamp":" 946820822685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820823730","data":{"timestamp":" 946820823730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820824210","data":{"timestamp":" 946820824210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820828770","data":{"timestamp":" 946820828768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820828901","data":{"timestamp":" 946820828901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" af2e3432-d318-4dc5-bf3b-c7fa252e96de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820839032","data":{"timestamp":" 946820839032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820839255","data":{"timestamp":" 946820839255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820840218","data":{"timestamp":" 946820840217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820841491","data":{"timestamp":" 946820841490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820844351","data":{"timestamp":" 946820844348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820845203","data":{"timestamp":" 946820845202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820845526","data":{"timestamp":" 946820845526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820846760","data":{"timestamp":" 946820846760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820850281","data":{"timestamp":" 946820850281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820851264","data":{"timestamp":" 946820851264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820851517","data":{"timestamp":" 946820851516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820852459","data":{"timestamp":" 946820852459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820855377","data":{"timestamp":" 946820855376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820856409","data":{"timestamp":" 946820856409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820856882","data":{"timestamp":" 946820856882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820861478","data":{"timestamp":" 946820861477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820861562","data":{"timestamp":" 946820861562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 6466f49d-b3f8-4665-9106-b34bfd0d1c6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820872136","data":{"timestamp":" 946820872135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820881076","data":{"timestamp":" 946820881076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820889080","data":{"timestamp":" 946820889080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820901448","data":{"timestamp":" 946820901448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820912755","data":{"timestamp":" 946820912755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820920064","data":{"timestamp":" 946820920064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820928277","data":{"timestamp":" 946820928277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820935940","data":{"timestamp":" 946820935940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820951192","data":{"timestamp":" 946820951192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820964198","data":{"timestamp":" 946820964198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820969953","data":{"timestamp":" 946820969952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820981881","data":{"timestamp":" 946820981880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" aaef4370-5db7-46a7-9e9c-9b8fb0451c8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820993189","data":{"timestamp":" 946820993187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820993366","data":{"timestamp":" 946820993366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820993697","data":{"timestamp":" 946820993696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820994860","data":{"timestamp":" 946820994859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820995600","data":{"timestamp":" 946820995599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820998945","data":{"timestamp":" 946820998945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821000715","data":{"timestamp":" 946821000714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821006395","data":{"timestamp":" 946821006395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821015260","data":{"timestamp":" 946821015260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821017283","data":{"timestamp":" 946821017283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821019797","data":{"timestamp":" 946821019796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821020440","data":{"timestamp":" 946821020439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821021235","data":{"timestamp":" 946821021235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821022078","data":{"timestamp":" 946821022078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821023010","data":{"timestamp":" 946821023010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821023702","data":{"timestamp":" 946821023702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821026063","data":{"timestamp":" 946821026062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821027347","data":{"timestamp":" 946821027347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821028699","data":{"timestamp":" 946821028699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821030773","data":{"timestamp":" 946821030772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821042401","data":{"timestamp":" 946821042401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821045420","data":{"timestamp":" 946821045420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821047864","data":{"timestamp":" 946821047863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821050147","data":{"timestamp":" 946821050147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821050842","data":{"timestamp":" 946821050842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821051856","data":{"timestamp":" 946821051855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821052029","data":{"timestamp":" 946821052029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821052782","data":{"timestamp":" 946821052782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821056897","data":{"timestamp":" 946821056897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821059947","data":{"timestamp":" 946821059947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821062403","data":{"timestamp":" 946821062403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821066868","data":{"timestamp":" 946821066868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821070084","data":{"timestamp":" 946821070084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821072519","data":{"timestamp":" 946821072519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821073332","data":{"timestamp":" 946821073332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821073396","data":{"timestamp":" 946821073396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821073978","data":{"timestamp":" 946821073978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821074570","data":{"timestamp":" 946821074570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821075364","data":{"timestamp":" 946821075363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821078861","data":{"timestamp":" 946821078861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821082203","data":{"timestamp":" 946821082203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821085243","data":{"timestamp":" 946821085243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821087578","data":{"timestamp":" 946821087578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821089413","data":{"timestamp":" 946821089413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821091691","data":{"timestamp":" 946821091690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821094442","data":{"timestamp":" 946821094442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821095064","data":{"timestamp":" 946821095064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821095727","data":{"timestamp":" 946821095726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821099556","data":{"timestamp":" 946821099556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821101655","data":{"timestamp":" 946821101655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821103783","data":{"timestamp":" 946821103782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821106012","data":{"timestamp":" 946821106012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821106903","data":{"timestamp":" 946821106903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821107996","data":{"timestamp":" 946821107996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821109169","data":{"timestamp":" 946821109169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821112137","data":{"timestamp":" 946821112137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821114180","data":{"timestamp":" 946821114180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821116832","data":{"timestamp":" 946821116832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821120236","data":{"timestamp":" 946821120236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821122957","data":{"timestamp":" 946821122956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821123340","data":{"timestamp":" 946821123340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821123958","data":{"timestamp":" 946821123958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821125162","data":{"timestamp":" 946821125162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821125806","data":{"timestamp":" 946821125806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821127249","data":{"timestamp":" 946821127249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821128091","data":{"timestamp":" 946821128091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821131616","data":{"timestamp":" 946821131616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821133047","data":{"timestamp":" 946821133046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821134923","data":{"timestamp":" 946821134923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821140425","data":{"timestamp":" 946821140424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821142458","data":{"timestamp":" 946821142458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821146167","data":{"timestamp":" 946821146167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821148517","data":{"timestamp":" 946821148517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821152324","data":{"timestamp":" 946821152324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821155019","data":{"timestamp":" 946821155019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821157282","data":{"timestamp":" 946821157281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821158262","data":{"timestamp":" 946821158262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821159144","data":{"timestamp":" 946821159144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821159798","data":{"timestamp":" 946821159798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821160839","data":{"timestamp":" 946821160838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821162130","data":{"timestamp":" 946821162129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821162155","data":{"timestamp":" 946821162155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821163020","data":{"timestamp":" 946821163020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821164113","data":{"timestamp":" 946821164113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821166876","data":{"timestamp":" 946821166876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821169151","data":{"timestamp":" 946821169151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821170868","data":{"timestamp":" 946821170868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821172589","data":{"timestamp":" 946821172588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821174881","data":{"timestamp":" 946821174881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821178573","data":{"timestamp":" 946821178572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821180361","data":{"timestamp":" 946821180361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821182274","data":{"timestamp":" 946821182274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821185556","data":{"timestamp":" 946821185556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821187304","data":{"timestamp":" 946821187304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821188047","data":{"timestamp":" 946821188047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821188900","data":{"timestamp":" 946821188900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821194114","data":{"timestamp":" 946821194114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821196891","data":{"timestamp":" 946821196891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821199888","data":{"timestamp":" 946821199888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821201294","data":{"timestamp":" 946821201294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821201837","data":{"timestamp":" 946821201837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821202600","data":{"timestamp":" 946821202600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821203119","data":{"timestamp":" 946821203118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821203909","data":{"timestamp":" 946821203908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821204583","data":{"timestamp":" 946821204583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821205437","data":{"timestamp":" 946821205437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821208457","data":{"timestamp":" 946821208457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821210676","data":{"timestamp":" 946821210676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821213056","data":{"timestamp":" 946821213055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821216375","data":{"timestamp":" 946821216375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821219834","data":{"timestamp":" 946821219834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821223172","data":{"timestamp":" 946821223172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821226866","data":{"timestamp":" 946821226866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821228977","data":{"timestamp":" 946821228977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821229770","data":{"timestamp":" 946821229770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821231353","data":{"timestamp":" 946821231351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821231585","data":{"timestamp":" 946821231585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821232132","data":{"timestamp":" 946821232131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821232936","data":{"timestamp":" 946821232936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821233563","data":{"timestamp":" 946821233562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821234623","data":{"timestamp":" 946821234623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821235106","data":{"timestamp":" 946821235106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821239830","data":{"timestamp":" 946821239830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821246877","data":{"timestamp":" 946821246877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821252173","data":{"timestamp":" 946821252173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821254169","data":{"timestamp":" 946821254169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821259598","data":{"timestamp":" 946821259597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821261204","data":{"timestamp":" 946821261204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821263104","data":{"timestamp":" 946821263104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821266221","data":{"timestamp":" 946821266221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821268875","data":{"timestamp":" 946821268875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821270534","data":{"timestamp":" 946821270534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821270947","data":{"timestamp":" 946821270947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821271493","data":{"timestamp":" 946821271493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821272846","data":{"timestamp":" 946821272846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821278807","data":{"timestamp":" 946821278807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821281312","data":{"timestamp":" 946821281312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821283341","data":{"timestamp":" 946821283341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821285382","data":{"timestamp":" 946821285382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821288052","data":{"timestamp":" 946821288048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821288986","data":{"timestamp":" 946821288985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821289727","data":{"timestamp":" 946821289726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821289960","data":{"timestamp":" 946821289959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821290563","data":{"timestamp":" 946821290563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821291421","data":{"timestamp":" 946821291420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821291602","data":{"timestamp":" 946821291602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821292217","data":{"timestamp":" 946821292217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821294058","data":{"timestamp":" 946821294058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821294850","data":{"timestamp":" 946821294849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821297970","data":{"timestamp":" 946821297970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821301519","data":{"timestamp":" 946821301519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821304657","data":{"timestamp":" 946821304656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821306458","data":{"timestamp":" 946821306458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821308726","data":{"timestamp":" 946821308726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821311297","data":{"timestamp":" 946821311296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821313208","data":{"timestamp":" 946821313208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821315559","data":{"timestamp":" 946821315558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821318243","data":{"timestamp":" 946821318243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821320660","data":{"timestamp":" 946821320660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821322901","data":{"timestamp":" 946821322900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821323734","data":{"timestamp":" 946821323733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821324386","data":{"timestamp":" 946821324385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821324990","data":{"timestamp":" 946821324989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821325380","data":{"timestamp":" 946821325380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821325582","data":{"timestamp":" 946821325582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821326313","data":{"timestamp":" 946821326312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821332804","data":{"timestamp":" 946821332804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821334921","data":{"timestamp":" 946821334921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821338310","data":{"timestamp":" 946821338310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821340227","data":{"timestamp":" 946821340226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821342375","data":{"timestamp":" 946821342375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821344031","data":{"timestamp":" 946821344031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821348360","data":{"timestamp":" 946821348360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821350458","data":{"timestamp":" 946821350458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821351128","data":{"timestamp":" 946821351127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821351972","data":{"timestamp":" 946821351972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821352685","data":{"timestamp":" 946821352685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821353480","data":{"timestamp":" 946821353479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821368992","data":{"timestamp":" 946821368992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821371519","data":{"timestamp":" 946821371519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821373985","data":{"timestamp":" 946821373985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821375940","data":{"timestamp":" 946821375940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821377691","data":{"timestamp":" 946821377691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821379521","data":{"timestamp":" 946821379520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821380694","data":{"timestamp":" 946821380694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821381468","data":{"timestamp":" 946821381468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821382231","data":{"timestamp":" 946821382231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821385829","data":{"timestamp":" 946821385829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821388158","data":{"timestamp":" 946821388158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821391151","data":{"timestamp":" 946821391151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821394011","data":{"timestamp":" 946821394011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821396205","data":{"timestamp":" 946821396205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821398579","data":{"timestamp":" 946821398578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821398600","data":{"timestamp":" 946821398600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821398621","data":{"timestamp":" 946821398621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821398627","data":{"timestamp":" 946821398627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821398642","data":{"timestamp":" 946821398642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821398660","data":{"timestamp":" 946821398660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821399527","data":{"timestamp":" 946821399527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821400390","data":{"timestamp":" 946821400390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821404694","data":{"timestamp":" 946821404694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821406199","data":{"timestamp":" 946821406199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821408294","data":{"timestamp":" 946821408293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821411778","data":{"timestamp":" 946821411778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821413511","data":{"timestamp":" 946821413511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821414887","data":{"timestamp":" 946821414887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821417379","data":{"timestamp":" 946821417379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821420289","data":{"timestamp":" 946821420289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821422275","data":{"timestamp":" 946821422275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821424499","data":{"timestamp":" 946821424499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821424983","data":{"timestamp":" 946821424983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821425726","data":{"timestamp":" 946821425726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821426789","data":{"timestamp":" 946821426789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821427193","data":{"timestamp":" 946821427193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821427896","data":{"timestamp":" 946821427896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821431911","data":{"timestamp":" 946821431910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821433864","data":{"timestamp":" 946821433864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821435434","data":{"timestamp":" 946821435434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821437901","data":{"timestamp":" 946821437900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821443457","data":{"timestamp":" 946821443456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821446543","data":{"timestamp":" 946821446543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821448975","data":{"timestamp":" 946821448975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821449919","data":{"timestamp":" 946821449919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821450653","data":{"timestamp":" 946821450653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821451296","data":{"timestamp":" 946821451296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821452199","data":{"timestamp":" 946821452199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821455208","data":{"timestamp":" 946821455208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821457812","data":{"timestamp":" 946821457812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821461361","data":{"timestamp":" 946821461361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821463459","data":{"timestamp":" 946821463459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821465250","data":{"timestamp":" 946821465250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821467218","data":{"timestamp":" 946821467218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821468020","data":{"timestamp":" 946821468020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821468834","data":{"timestamp":" 946821468834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821472679","data":{"timestamp":" 946821472679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821475644","data":{"timestamp":" 946821475644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821477761","data":{"timestamp":" 946821477761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821479599","data":{"timestamp":" 946821479598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821480219","data":{"timestamp":" 946821480219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821480805","data":{"timestamp":" 946821480804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821481789","data":{"timestamp":" 946821481789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821482698","data":{"timestamp":" 946821482697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821483761","data":{"timestamp":" 946821483761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821484349","data":{"timestamp":" 946821484349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821487843","data":{"timestamp":" 946821487843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821490885","data":{"timestamp":" 946821490885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821492542","data":{"timestamp":" 946821492542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821494686","data":{"timestamp":" 946821494686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821496664","data":{"timestamp":" 946821496664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821498827","data":{"timestamp":" 946821498827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821500828","data":{"timestamp":" 946821500827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821502873","data":{"timestamp":" 946821502873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821503039","data":{"timestamp":" 946821503039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" c128ade2-ccc3-4cf0-bd61-66ccd0a5b35c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821512226","data":{"timestamp":" 946821512225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821512450","data":{"timestamp":" 946821512450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821513434","data":{"timestamp":" 946821513434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821514708","data":{"timestamp":" 946821514708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821517601","data":{"timestamp":" 946821517600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821518462","data":{"timestamp":" 946821518462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821518784","data":{"timestamp":" 946821518783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821520028","data":{"timestamp":" 946821520027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821523471","data":{"timestamp":" 946821523471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821524459","data":{"timestamp":" 946821524459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821524714","data":{"timestamp":" 946821524714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821525657","data":{"timestamp":" 946821525657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821528510","data":{"timestamp":" 946821528510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821529544","data":{"timestamp":" 946821529543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821530016","data":{"timestamp":" 946821530016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821534533","data":{"timestamp":" 946821534533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821534597","data":{"timestamp":" 946821534597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" f2217a2e-c539-4b90-a23b-bf67eab94699"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821562359","data":{"timestamp":" 946821562358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimwona_alimwona-mlangoni-kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimwona"," userResponse":" alimwona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821567940","data":{"timestamp":" 946821567940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" kumfanya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821575499","data":{"timestamp":" 946821575499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" tabasamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821584136","data":{"timestamp":" 946821584136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821592072","data":{"timestamp":" 946821592071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821599538","data":{"timestamp":" 946821599538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821605321","data":{"timestamp":" 946821605321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" b56b9cf9-ced8-47e3-84eb-8116f1bd0736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821623384","data":{"timestamp":" 946821623384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821624200","data":{"timestamp":" 946821624200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821625444","data":{"timestamp":" 946821625444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821626358","data":{"timestamp":" 946821626358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821627216","data":{"timestamp":" 946821627216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821640248","data":{"timestamp":" 946821640247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821648528","data":{"timestamp":" 946821648528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821649462","data":{"timestamp":" 946821649462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821650838","data":{"timestamp":" 946821650838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821651358","data":{"timestamp":" 946821651358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821655595","data":{"timestamp":" 946821655595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821661868","data":{"timestamp":" 946821661868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821662476","data":{"timestamp":" 946821662475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821662900","data":{"timestamp":" 946821662900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821668891","data":{"timestamp":" 946821668891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821669416","data":{"timestamp":" 946821669416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821674300","data":{"timestamp":" 946821674300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821674856","data":{"timestamp":" 946821674856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821675939","data":{"timestamp":" 946821675939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821676822","data":{"timestamp":" 946821676822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821682731","data":{"timestamp":" 946821682731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821683839","data":{"timestamp":" 946821683839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821685180","data":{"timestamp":" 946821685180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821686338","data":{"timestamp":" 946821686338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821690003","data":{"timestamp":" 946821690002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821690761","data":{"timestamp":" 946821690761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821691861","data":{"timestamp":" 946821691861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821692727","data":{"timestamp":" 946821692727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821696918","data":{"timestamp":" 946821696918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821697843","data":{"timestamp":" 946821697843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821698559","data":{"timestamp":" 946821698559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821699251","data":{"timestamp":" 946821699251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821702960","data":{"timestamp":" 946821702960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821703633","data":{"timestamp":" 946821703632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821704124","data":{"timestamp":" 946821704124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821704532","data":{"timestamp":" 946821704532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821708425","data":{"timestamp":" 946821708425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821709198","data":{"timestamp":" 946821709198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821709589","data":{"timestamp":" 946821709589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821710098","data":{"timestamp":" 946821710097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821713773","data":{"timestamp":" 946821713773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821714246","data":{"timestamp":" 946821714246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821714746","data":{"timestamp":" 946821714746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821715046","data":{"timestamp":" 946821715046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821717273","data":{"timestamp":" 946821717273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_164244"," gameId":" 49b70b41-c2e8-4a84-be25-0d9bb29a4536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}